제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
위스콘신주 포인트 플레이스
Point Place, Wisconsin
에릭네 지하실
Eric Forman's Basement
졸업무도회 주간
Prom Week
금요일 오후 7시 46분
Thursday, 7:46 p.m.
내 첫 졸업무도회복이야
My first prom tux.
얘들아, 빛나는 벨벳재킷을 보시라
Come on, guys,
dig the crushed velvet.
에릭, 너 삐끼같아
Eric, you look like a pimp.
야, 포먼
You know, Forman...
졸업무도회는 너하고 도나에게
특별한 밤이 될 수도 있어
prom night could be a very
special night for you and Donna.
우리 인생에서 가장 역사적인
밤이 될지도 몰라
Hyde, this could
be the biggest night of our lives.
- 그러니까, 우린..
- 무도회에 가지
- I mean, Donna and I could go--
- To the prom.
- 아니, 우린 끝까지 갈 거야
- 끝까지..
- No, Fez. All the way.
- All the way..
무도회에 가지
to the prom.
내가 시키는 대로 해
모텔 방을 잡는 거야
You know what you should do?
You should rent a motel room.
그래, 퍽도 자연스럽다
Yeah, that's spontaneous.
뭐가?
What?
그날 밤 내 생각대로 잘 된다면
난 아주 아주 특별하게 하고 싶어
Look, if this night is as big as I think,
I want it to be very, very special.
왜냐면 이건 우리 둘다
첫경험이 될테니까
Because this is gonna be
the first time for both of us.
어린 것들 순진하기는
You silly virgins.
어쨌든 내 생각은 대충 이런 거야
Anyway, this is how I picture it.
해변을 산책하다
여기까지 와 버렸네
Well, here we are...
walking on the beach.
이제 우린 그걸 할 거야
And now we're gonna do it.
그럼, 그럼
Yes, yes.
너무 자연스럽지 않니?
Isn't it spontaneous?
맞아. 그래서 내가
너한테 빠져버린 걸
Exactly. That's what got me.
아, 너무 좋았어
That was nice.
그런데 계획을 세우면
별로 안 좋을 거야. 아마 이렇게..
But if I plan it out, it won't be nice.
It'll be....
- 안녕하십니까?
- 서류는 다 준비됐나?
- Good evening.
- Did you bring the forms?
네. 이건 전희 보증서입니다
Yes, I did.
Here's the guarantee of foreplay.
서명, 날인, 공증 다 했습니다
Signed, initialed, notarized.
아주 좋아
Very well. As you know,
I'm on the pill...
알다시피 난 피임약 복용중이라서
여기 피임 면제 증서 사본이야
so here is your copy
of the prophylactic waiver.
계약이 체결된 거 같군요
목표 달성을 기대하겠습니다
It looks like we have a deal here.
I'm looking forward to consummation.
- 좋아
- 감사합니다
- Excellent.
- Thank you.
포먼, 모텔방 안 잡았다가는
이렇게 될 수도 있어
Forman, if you don't get a motel,
it's gonna be more like this.
너 벌써 집에 온 거냐?
10시도 안 됐는데
You're home already?
It's not even 10:00.
너 계획도 안 세웠었지, 그렇지?
You didn't have a plan, did you?
여보, 이 녀석 벌써 왔구려
Kitty, he's home already.
벌써요? 에릭, 너 정말 한심하구나
Already? Eric, you're
just such a loser.
정말 한심해, 그렇지?
He is, isn't he?
토퍼 그레이스 (에릭 포먼)
밀라 커니스 (재키 벅하트)
애쉬튼 커쳐 (마이클 켈소)
대니 메스털슨 (스티븐 하이드)
로라 프레폰 (도나 핀씨오티)
윌머 발더라마 (페즈)
데브라 조 러프 (키티 포먼)
커트우드 스미스 (레드 포먼)
타냐 로버츠 (미지 핀씨오티)
돈 스탁 (밥 핀씨오티)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정, 번역 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
1x19 Prom Night
Mar 07, 1999 on FOX
키티, 밥 때문에 미치겠어요
Kitty, I am so mad at Bob.
난 자기개발을 하고 싶은데
그이가 못하게 해요
I'm trying to improve myself,
and he won't let me.
게다가, 절더러 바보같대요
Plus, he says my ideas are stupid.
똥묻은 개가 겨묻은 개 나무라고
있네요, 그렇지 않아요 ?
Now that's the pot calling
the kettle black, isn't it?
내 말이요
I'll say.
뭐라구요?
What?
맛있는 커피라고요
Good coffee.
있죠, 미안해요, 미지
일하러 가봐야겠어요
You know, I'm sorry, Midge.
But I really have to get to work.
젠장, 나도 일하고 싶다구요
Gosh, darn it, I want a job.
미지, 일을 한다는 건
폼 나기만 한 게 아니에요
You know, Midge, having a job
is not all it's cracked up to be.
병원에서 일하는 건
정말 힘들어요
Working at the hospital
is very hard work.
그치만 힘든 일이 아니라
재밌는 일을 할거예요
But I don't want one of those jobs.
I want a fun job.
아무리 재밌는 일이라도..
Okay, even with a fun job, you still....
상사 비위는 맞춰야 돼요
You have to deal with your boss.
그러네요
You're right. I'll get a job as a boss.
맞다! 그럼 나 사장이 될래요
정말 빈틈없는 계획이네요, 미지
Now, that is a sharp plan, Midge.
있죠, 어떻게 돼가는지
나한테도 알려줘요
You just.... You let me
know how that goes.
얘들아, 팸 메이시의
졸업무도회 파트너가 누구게?
Okay, guys. Guess who's taking
Pam Macy to the prom?
25 센트만 있으면 아무나?
Anyone with a quarter?
나야
Me.
아깝다, 나도 25 센트 있는데
Damn, and I had a quarter.
- 너 재키 안 데려갈 거야?
- 말도 안돼
- Kelso, you're not taking Jackie?
- No way, man.
재키는 날 찼단 말야
Jackie dumped me.
내가 데려갈 수도 있어
I can take Jackie.
그래, 그래 봐, 페즈
가만 안둘 줄 알아
Yeah, do it, Fez,
and I'll kick your ass.
이런, 이런, 이런
Well, well, well.
갑자기 웬 관심이셔?
Look who suddenly cares.
왜 때려?
그냥 빈정거린 건데
Why did you hit me?
That was sarcasm.
너희들이 졸업무도회 얘기만 하니까
정말 짜증이 난다
You know, you guys are making
me sick with all your prom talk.
졸업무도회는 바보짓이야
Proms are stupid.
네가 그걸 어떻게 알아?
넌 가본 적도 없잖아
What would you know?
You've never even been to one.
난 치과에도 가본 적 없지만
거기가 짜증난다는 건 안단다
I haven't been to the dentist, either,
but I don't need to go to know it's lame.
오, 누구랑 무도회 갈지 알았다
I know who I can ask to the prom.
오! 그러셔, 누군데, 페즈?
Oh, boy, who, Fez?
그 행운의 주인공은..
The lucky lady is...
영어 선생님
my English teacher.
페즈, 졸업무도회에
선생님은 못 데려가는 거야
Fez, you can't take
a teacher to the prom.
왜 안돼? 내 숙제에다 매번
야한 코멘트를 달아주신단 말야
Why not? She's always writing
sexy comments on my homework.
들어봐
See.
"잘 했어요"
"Nice job.
"노력이 돋보이네요"
Good effort.
"끝나고 남아요"
"See me.
"사랑해요"
"I love you."
그래, 마지막 건
내가 지어낸 거지만
Okay, I made the last one up...
다른 건 다 정말이야
but the other ones were real.
졸업무도회 때 이 신발을 신을 거야
These are the shoes
I'm wearing to the prom.
괜찮지 않니?
Aren't they cool?
어머, 나도 새 신발 사려고 했는데..
My God. I was gonna
get new shoes...
마이클이 같이 가자고만 했으면
except Michael didn't ask me.
내 무도회 드레스도
맘에 들거야, 그렇지?
And you like my prom dress, right?
어머, 나도 무도회 드레스
새로 사려고 했는데..
My God.
I was gonna get a new prom dress...
마이클이 같이 가자고만 했으면
except Michael didn't ask me.
졸업무도회 때문에 너무 긴장돼
I'm so nervous about the prom.
내 생각엔 그날밤에 에릭이랑 내가..
I think it's gonna be
the night that Eric and I....
알지?
You know?
어머머, 마이클이랑 나도 첫경험을
그날밤 할려고 했었는데
My gosh, that's when Michael and I
were going to do it for the first time.
재키, 너희들은 두달전에 벌써 했잖아
Jackie, you and Kelso did it,
like, two months ago.
그 뒤로 30번 쯤은 더 했고
And, like, 30 times after that.
그래, 그래도 졸업무도회에서
하는 건 처음일 거 아냐
Yeah, but it would have been
our first time at a prom.
마이클이 같이 가자고만 했으면
Except Michael didn't ask me.
재키, 네가 찼잖아
Jackie, you broke up with him.
나도 알아
너무 슬프지 않니?
I know. Isn't it sad?
그냥 켈소한테 같이 가자고 해
Look, just ask Kelso to go with you.
절대 안돼. 이건 졸업무도회야
God, no. This is the prom.
멍청한 너희 페미니스트들이
나설 자리가 아니란 말야
This is no time
for your stupid feminist crap.
안녕, 마이클?
Hello, Michael.
안녕, 재키?
Hello, Jackie.
난 그냥 도나 졸업무도회 준비
도와주러 온 거야
I'm just over here helping Donna
get ready for the prom.
왜냐면 도나랑 에릭은
졸업무도회 갈 거니까
Because Eric and Donna
are going to the prom.
맞는 말이야
Yes, we are.
나도 갈 거야
I'm going to the prom.
난 팸 메이시랑 갈 거야
I'm taking Pam Macy.
아, 할 일이 있었지?
Oh, the thing.
나도 같이 갈 사람 있어
I have a date, too.
누구야? 그 자식 이름이 뭐야?
Who is it? What's his name?
이름은..
His name is not important.
중요하지 않아
중요한 건 너보다 잘 났다는 거야
What's important is,
he's better than you...
모든 면에서 말야
in every conceivable way.
젠장, 재키
그럼 아무나 된단 얘기잖아!
Damn, Jackie,
that could be anybody!
재키..
Jackie...
무슨 일인지 물어봐 주면
그거 그만 해 줄거냐?
if I asked you what's wrong,
will you stop doing that?
졸업무도회 말야. 멍청한 마이클이
멍청한 팸 메이시를 데리고 간데
It's the prom. Stupid Michael's
taking stupid Pam Macy.
난 같이 갈 사람도 없는데 있다고
말해 버렸거든, 완전 바보됐어
And I don't have a date, but I told
him I did, and I'm a complete loser.
아냐, 바보 아냐
No, you're not.
아니긴, 난 마이클이
같이 가자고 할 줄 알았어
It's just that, like,
I thought he was gonna ask me...
지금은 갈 만한 해들은
다 짝이 있단 말야
and now everyone who's anyone
is already going.
그건 그래
That is so true.
넌 어떻게 알아?
넌 가지도 않잖아
How would you know?
You're not even going.
오, 너 안간다면서
왜 그렇게 깨끗이 씼었어?
You're not even going.
And I bet you clean up real good.
글쎄, 씼긴 했지만 난 안가
Well, I do, but I won't.
그게 바로 나야
See, that's a big part of who I am.
우리가 다른 점이 좀 있는 건
알지만, 그래도..
Look, I know we've had
our differences, but--
재키, 우린 다른 점 밖에 없어
Jackie, we've had nothing
but differences.
사실, 우린 서로 미워하는 거 아녔나?
In fact, don't we kind of
hate each other?
그래도 졸업무도회잖아
Yes, but this is the prom.
재키
Jackie,
그만
stop.
그만 울어. 그만 해
Stop crying. Stop it.
야, 졸업무도회 같이 갈래? / 그래
Look, do you want to
go to the prom? / Yes.
"Slow Ride" by Foghat
우와, 체육관이 마치..
The gym looks like....
체육관에 리본 좀
두른 거 치곤.. 괜찮네
Well, the gym with streamers.
But it's nice.
그래. 오늘은 잊지 못할 밤이 될거야
Yeah. You know, this is just
gonna be an incredible night.
정말 잊지 못할 거야
Really incredible.
잠깐. 무슨 뜻이야?
Wait. What do you mean?
넌 무슨 뜻이었는데?
What do you mean?
- 아무 것도 아냐
- 그럼 나도 아무것도 아냐
- Nothing.
- Okay, then me neither.
얘들아, 팸
여긴 에릭이랑 도나
Hey, guys. Pam,
this is Eric and Donna.
우린 생물 수업 같이 들어
We have biology class together.
생물?
Biology?
그래
Yeah.
있잖아, 팸은 학교 얘기 싫어해
See, Pam doesn't like to
talk about school.
- 재밌게 보내고 있니?
- 아니
- Are you guys having fun?
- No.
화장실에 가야 겠다
I have to go to the bathroom.
야, 켈소, 너 쟤가 재키보다
낫다는 거야?
My God, Kelso, you'd rather
be with her than Jackie?
- 난 쟤를 사랑해!
- 사랑은 무슨..
- I love her!
- No, you don't.
맞아, 사랑 안해
Okay, I don't.
그래도 재키는 엄청 질투할거야
See, but Jackie's gonna
be really jealous.
안녕, 얘들아
다들 재미있니?
Good evening, kids.
So, is everyone having fun?
네, 재밌어요. 카민스키 선생님
Why, yes, we are, Ms. Kaminsky.
여기 있었구려, 다이안
내내 당신을 찾고 있었다오
There you are, Diane.
I've been looking all over for you.
같이 춤 추실래요?
Shall we dance?
난 너랑 춤 안 출 거야, 페즈
I am not going to
dance with you, Fez.
너무 사랑스럽지 않아?
Isn't she adorable?
다들 너보고 웃을 거야!
They're all gonna laugh at you!
닥쳐요, 엄마
오늘 밤 너무 신나신 거 아니에요?
Shut up, Ma, you're making
the night too damn special.
우와, 너 정말 예쁘다
You look beautiful.
어머, 너도 멋있어
My God. So do you.
들어가서 너희 엄마한테 인사라도..
Do you want me to go inside
and meet your....
아냐. 괜찮아, 지금 신나셨거든
No. Trust me, she's lovely.
그냥 가자, 됐지?
Let's just go, all right?
그거 나 줄 거니?
Is that for me?
아, 이거, 널 위해 준비했어
Yeah. Here, I got this for you.
어머, 스티븐, 너무 예쁘다
God, Steven, this is beautiful.
난 이번에 마이클이 없어도
졸업무도회 갈 수 있다는 걸 알았어
This whole experience has taught me
that I don't need Michael to go to the prom.
난 누구하고도 갈 수 있어
I can go with anyone.
너하고도
Even you.
고마워
Thanks.
이런건 하지 말자
Okay, let's not do that.
미안해. 아빠 링컨을 타고 왔는데
네가 운전할래?
Sorry. I have my dad's Lincoln.
Will you drive?
그럼. 보험은 드셨겠지?
Yeah. He's got insurance, right?
잠깐, 상관없어. 가자
Wait, I don't care. Let's go.
어떤 사업을 할 건지 결정했어요
I've decided what kind of
business I'm going to open.
사람들이 사는데
꼭 필요한 게 뭘까요?
What's the one thing
people can't live without?
산소요
Oxygen.
아뇨
No.
아니긴요, 맞아요
No. That's true.
그래도 내가 팔려는 건 아니니까
계속 생각해 보세요
But that's not what I'm selling.
So keep guessing.
레몬에이드?
Lemonade?
포기예요?
Give up?
그럴까봐
I'm about to.
축하 카드요
Greeting cards.
맛있는 와인
Good wine.
"I'm not in Love" by 10CC
너무 멋진 밤이다
This is such a great night.
그래
Yeah.
우리 부모님이 놀러 안 가셔서
너무 아쉬워
It's too bad our parents
aren't out of town.
그랬으면 우리가
갈 곳이 생겼을텐데
So we'd have someplace to go.
이거 끝나고 말야
For after.
그래. 뭐..
Yeah. Like,
모텔 방 같은 데?
a motel room?
그래. 그것도 멋질 것 같다
Yeah. That would've been great.
정말? 내가 하나 잡아놨거든
Really? 'Cause I got one.
원래 나한테 말할 계획이었니?
Did you plan on telling me?
아니
No.
말 안 하기로 한건 잘했어
It's better that you didn't.
그게 더 자연스럽잖아
'Cause then
it wouldn't have been spontaneous.
우린 정말 잘 맞는다니까
You are so the girl for me.
가자
Let's go.
좋아
Okay.
왜 풀이 죽어 있니, 페즈?
Why so glum, Fez?
클라크 선생님, 음악 가르치는 건
잘 하실지 몰라도
Mrs. Clark, you may be good
at teaching the music...
제 사랑의 아픔은 해결해
주실 수 없을 거예요
but you cannot help me
in the ways of love.
페즈, 누가 널 슬프게 하니?
Fez, has someone got you down?
장난 아니게요
So far down, Mrs. Clark.
내가 준비해 온 노래가 하나 있는데
아마 도움이 될 거다
Here's a little ditty I've been
working on. Maybe it'll help.
시작해요
Hit it.
"l Will Survive" by Gloria Gaynor
실제 Gloria Gaynor 입니다
♪ 처음에 난 두렵고 놀랐어 ♪
♪ First I was afraid,
I was petrified. ♪
♪ 당신 없이는 살 수 없을 것만 같았지 ♪
♪ Kept thinking I could never live
without you by my side. ♪
♪ 하지만 당신이 내게 한 잘못을
생각하느라 수많은 밤을 지새우면서 ♪
♪ But I spent so many nights
thinking how you did me wrong. ♪
♪ 난 점점 강해졌어 ♪
♪ I grew strong. ♪
♪ 어떻게 살아야 할지 깨달았지
그러다 당신이 돌아왔어 ♪
♪ I learned how to carry on and
so you're back ♪
♪ 다른 세상에서 말야 ♪
♪ from outer space. ♪
♪ 집에 와보니
당신의 처량한 모습이 보이더군 ♪
♪ I just walked in to find you here
with that sad look upon your face. ♪
♪ 자물쇠를 바꿨어야 했는데 ♪
♪ I should have changed
my stupid lock. ♪
♪ 당신 열쇠를 뺐었어야 했는데 ♪
♪ I should have made
you leave your key. ♪
♪ 당신이 돌아와서 날 귀찮게 할 줄
알았으면 말야 ♪
♪ If I had known for just one second
you'd be back to bother me. ♪
♪ 가버려, 당장 가 ♪
♪ Go on now go, ♪
♪ 저 문으로 나가 ♪
♪ walk out the door, ♪
♪ 당장 돌아서서 가란 말야 ♪
♪ just turn around now. ♪
♪ 난 더이상 당신을 원치 않으니까 ♪
♪ 'Cause you're not
welcome anymore. ♪
♪ 내게 이별의 상처를
주려던 건 당신 아니었나? ♪
♪ Weren't you the one who tried
to hurt me with goodbye? ♪
♪ 내가 무너졌을 거라 생각했어? ♪
♪ You think I'd crumble. ♪
♪ 내가 쓰러져 죽었을 거라 생각했어? ♪
♪ You think I'd lay down and die. ♪
♪ 아니, 난 아냐! ♪
♪ Oh no, not I! ♪
♪ 난 괜찮아 ♪
♪ I will survive. ♪
여보, 당신은 사업에 대해
아무 것도 몰라
Midge, you don't know the first thing
about having a business.
- 그치만 밑져야 본전인데요, 뭐
- 왜?
- But there's no risk, Bob.
- Why not?
당신 돈이니까요!
Because it's your money!
키티, 자기도 내가
카드가게하는 거 반대해요?
Kitty, don't you think I should have
my own card shop?
미지, 잠깐만
Midgie, hold on.
확실한 해결책이 떠올랐어 / 정말요?
I think I have
a dynamite solution. / Really?
그래. 난 당신을 사랑하잖아
Yeah. 'Cause I love you.
아이를 하나 더 낳아서
날 그만 괴롭히는 거야
So, I want you to have another baby
and stop bugging me.
오, 밥. 안돼요
Oh, Bob. No.
그래서 다 차려주는 데
얼마나 들것 같은가, 밥?
So, how much this whole setup
gonna cost you, Bob?
꽤 많이
Plenty. But I figure it'll be
cheaper than a divorce.
그래도 이혼보다는 싸게
먹힐 거라고 봐
그거야 두고 보세
We'll see.
다 왔어
And here we are.
너무 낭만적이야
This is so romantic.
야, 포먼이랑 도나다
쟤네 그거 할 건가 봐!
It's Forman and Donna.
And they're gonna do it!
포먼! 포먼!
Forman! Forman!
Yeah.
저 자식들은 바보들이니까
신경쓰지 마
You know what?
Those guys are just jerks.
벌써 다 잊었어
I forgot about them already.
잠깐, 잠깐
커다란 얼룩이야
Hang on. Big stain.
가서 수건 가져올게 / 알았어
- I'm just gonna go grab a towel.
- Okay.
엄마야!
Good God!
쟤들이 오히려
나보다 더 놀란 거 같아
They say they're more scared of you
than you are of them. Right, so?
있지, 도나
계속 이 순간을 생각해 왔어
You know, Donna,
I've thought about this moment...
수없이 많이
like, a thousand times.
나도
Me, too.
하나, 둘, 셋
One, two, three.
좋았어
All right.
네가 이 순간을 상상할 때도
이랬었니?
When you thought about this moment,
was it like this?
아니
Not really.
파티장에 있을 땐 좋았었는데
You know, I was having
a pretty good time at prom.
나도
Me, too.
나가자
Let's get out of here.
좋아
Okay.
도나, 이게 우리의
유일한 기회였으면 어쩌지?
Donna, what if this is our only chance?
걱정 마
It won't be.
좋아
Okay.
"Freebird" by Lynyrd Skynyrd
난 항상 마이클하고 졸업무도회에
오게 될 거라고 생각했었어
It's just that I always pictured
Michael and I together at the prom.
그땐 그게 당연했으니까, 알지?
That's the way
it was supposed to be, you know?
그래
Yeah, I know.
근데..
Well...
저 드레스 입으니까
팸 엉덩이 정말 커 보인다
Pam's butt looks
really big in that dress.
천만에, 아냐
No, it doesn't.
아니긴..
그래, 아닌 것 같다
Yeah, no, it doesn't.
어쨌든 고마워
But thank you.
그만 들어가서 앉으면 안될까?
Do you mind if we just sit down?
그래, 좋아
내가 펀치를 좀 갖다줄께
Yeah, okay. I'll go grab some punch.
하이드, 니가 재키랑 여길 와?
Hyde, you brought Jackie to the prom?
난 네가 친군 줄 알았는데
내 뒤통수를 치다니
You're supposed to be my friend
and you dogged me.
우는 걸 어떡해?
She cried, man.
즐거워 하는 것 같아?
Is she having a good time?
오늘 너무 예뻐 보인다
'Cause she looks real pretty.
알았어. 이 덜떨어진 놈아
All right, look, you big baby.
쟤도 너처럼
너랑 같이 있고 싶어해
She wants to be with you,
and you want to be with her.
그러니까 그만 징징거리고 가봐
So, why don't you stop whining about it
and just go be with each other.
전부 아주 짜증나 죽겠어
'Cause the whole thing sickens me.
그럼 팸은 어떡하지?
But what am I gonna do with Pam?
그건 걱정마
팸은 내가 알아서 할게
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of Pam.
실례할께, 팸
Excuse me, Pam.
안녕?
Hi.
링컨 콘티넨탈 뒷좌석 본 적 있니?
Have you ever seen
the backseat of a Lincoln Continental?
많이 봤어
Lots of times.
그럼 한번 더 보지 않을래?
Would you like to see another one?
좋아
Sure.
좋았어. 가자
That's great. Let's go.
재키
Jackie.
마이클
Michael.
너 너무 아름답다
You look beautiful.
너도 정말 멋있어
You look really handsome.
니가 그리웠어
I miss you.
나도 네가 그리웠어
I miss you, too.
에릭, 모텔방 열쇠 나 주면 안돼?
Eric, please may I have
your motel room key, please?
페즈, 난 너랑 모텔에 안 갈 거야
Fez, I'm not going to a motel with you.
네, 춤도 안 출거라고
하셨지만 이렇게 추잖아요
Yes, and you also said
you would not dance with me.
번역수정: 김찬미 (husseyttl@nate)
최종수정: 김현정 (fuchs@nate)
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24